The course of true love never did run smooth, Lysander tells us in Shakespeare's A Midsummer Night's Dream.
莱桑德在莎士比亚的《仲夏夜之梦》中说道：“真爱之路从不平坦。”
Wise words, many would say.
很多人都会说，这是至理名言。
In the fast-paced world of modern life, it can be difficult to meet anyone, let alone our soulmate.
在快节奏的现代生活中，遇见一个人都很难，更别说遇见灵魂伴侣了。
Fortunately, there's an app for that, though wooing a potential partner is still up to you.
幸运的是，有一款应用可以帮你解决这个问题，不过追求潜在伴侣仍然要靠你自己。
Dating apps like Tinder, Bumble and Chappy have been around for a good few years and statistics prove their ongoing popularity.
Tinder、Bumble和Chappy等约会应用已经存在好几年了，数据证明它们一直很受欢迎。
Tinder claims to get 1.6 billion swipes per day.
Tinder声称每天的滑动次数达16亿次。
A study conducted by globaldatinginsights.com, analysts of the online dating industry, found that lonely hearts in the UK spent 10 hours a week using them to find someone to go out with.
在线约会行业分析机构globaldatinginsights.com开展的一项研究发现，英国的单身人士每周会花10个小时使用这些应用寻找约会对象。
And finally, a 2018 YouGov survey conducted on behalf of BBC Radio 1 Newsbeat found that of over 2000 16-34-year-olds, nearly half had used a dating app at some point.
最后，2018年舆观调查公司（YouGov）代表英国广播公司第一电台《新闻节拍》节目开展的一项调查显示，在2000多名16至34岁的受访者中，近一半人曾在某一时期使用过约会应用。
That said, the very same survey found that only 17% had met their current beau on an app.
尽管如此，同一项调查发现，只有17%的人是在应用上遇到了现在的伴侣。
And 37% said that using an app was their least preferred method to find a potential mate to take out, for a fling or otherwise.
37%的人表示，无论是寻找约会对象、短暂恋情对象还是其他关系对象，使用应用都是他们最不喜欢的方式。
One possible reason for this comes from one respondent, 26-year-old Jordan.
26岁的受访者乔丹给出了其中一个可能的原因。
He believes that dating apps create issues with self-doubt and anxiety.
他认为约会应用会引发自我怀疑和焦虑问题。
"You're judged for the person you are on screen and not for the person you are," he told the BBC.
“人们评判的是屏幕上的你，而不是真实的你，”他告诉英国广播公司。
As people open themselves up to more rejection, it can lead to feelings of depression, says relationship psychologist Madeleine Mason Roantree.
情感心理学家玛德琳·梅森·罗恩特里表示，当人们面临更多拒绝时，可能会产生抑郁情绪。
Indeed, Jordan says he's been judged on dating apps for being "too young, too old and too fat."
事实上，乔丹说自己在约会应用上曾因“太年轻、太老、太胖”而受到评判。
Deception can be another issue, with profiles often stretching the truth.
欺骗是另一个问题，用户资料往往会夸大事实。
Twenty-year-old Emma told Newsbeat about meeting a suitor whose height matched hers on their profiles, only to find he was a foot shorter in reality.
20岁的艾玛告诉《新闻节拍》，她曾遇到一个追求者，资料上显示两人身高相同，结果发现他实际上比自己矮一英尺。
Twenty-four-year-old Mikey believes dating apps are "quite Catfish-y" after meeting someone whose profile picture did not match their appearance.
24岁的米奇在遇到一个个人资料照片与本人不符的人后，认为约会应用“很容易出现虚假信息”。
So does this mean that dating apps are a waste of time?
那么，这是否意味着约会应用是在浪费时间？
It depends.
这取决于具体情况。
Over 25% of those asked by YouGov might not agree.
舆观调查公司（YouGov）的受访者中，超过25%的人可能不会同意这种说法。
They were going steady or had tied the knot as a result of a dating app.
他们通过约会应用确定了稳定关系，甚至步入了婚姻殿堂。
A happily ever after might only be round the corner, but one way to find out is to swipe right and see.
幸福的结局可能就在眼前，而验证这一点的方法之一就是右滑试试。